{
    "q1": {
        "id": "q1",
        "question": "What are Harry Potter's parents names?",
        "answers": [
            "James and Lily",
            "Voldemort and Bellatrix",
            "Remus and Nymphadora",
            "Arthur and Molly"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "James and Lily"
    },
    "q2": {
        "id": "q2",
        "question": "What was Hagrid's pet dog called?",
        "answers": [
            "Dobby",
            "Scabbers",
            "Fang",
            "Hedwig"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Fang"
    },
    "q3": {
        "id": "q3",
        "question": "Name the killing Curse",
        "answers": [
            "Lumos",
            "Avada Kedavra",
            "Crucio",
            "Imperio"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Avada Kedavra"
    },
    "q4": {
        "id": "q4",
        "question": "What spell would you use to open a door?",
        "answers": [
            "Riddikulus",
            "Lumos",
            "Alohomora",
            "Expelliarmus"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Alohomora"
    },
    "q5": {
        "id": "q5",
        "question": "What is Harry's relation to Serius Black",
        "answers": [
            "Uncle",
            "Father",
            "Brother",
            "Godfather"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Godfather"
    },
    "q6": {
        "id": "q6",
        "question": "What is a Horcrux?",
        "answers": [
            "An object formed by dark magic",
            "A stone that gives the owner great power",
            "A type of snake",
            "An object that makes you invisible"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "An object formed by dark magic"
    },
    "q7": {
        "id": "q7",
        "question": "What is the Longest Harry Potter book?",
        "answers": [
            "Harry Potter and The Deathly Hollows",
            "Harry Potter and the Philosophers Stone",
            "Harry Potter and The Goblet of Fire",
            "Harry Potter and The Order of the Phoenix"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Harry Potter and The Order of the Phoenix"
    },
    "q8": {
        "id": "q8",
        "question": "What are the Deathly Hollows?",
        "answers": [
            "A spooky story",
            "Objects that are collected to make one the master of death",
            "A pub where Witches and Wizards like to go to hang out",
            "A secret group of Witches and wizards that control what really happens in the world"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Objects that are collected to make one the master of death"
    },
    "q9": {
        "id": "q9",
        "question": "What was Harry Potters Patronus",
        "answers": [
            "Stag",
            "Otter",
            "Black Swan",
            "Mouse"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Stag"
    },
    "q10": {
        "id": "q10",
        "question": "Where do the Dursley's live",
        "answers": [
            "4 Privet Drive",
            "10 Privet Drive",
            "11 Privet Drive",
            "6 Privet Drive"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "4 Privet Drive"
    }
}